{"question": "What is the postal code range of Kropotkin, Krasnodar Krai, Russia", "answer": "352380-352396", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kropotkin,_Krasnodar_Krai#cite_note-PostalCode-6", "timestamp": "2025-08-27T13:12:45.491003"}
{"question": "In what year did Anna-Lena Fritzon achieve her best result at the FIS Cross-Country World Cup", "answer": "1988", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anna-Lena_Fritzon", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:07:57.233280"}
{"question": "On what day was the asteroid 69230 Hermes first discovered", "answer": "28 October 1937", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/69230_Hermes", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:07:58.893731"}
{"question": "In which borough is the John Rankin House, designated a New York City landmark in 1970", "answer": "Brooklyn", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Rankin_House_(Brooklyn)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:08:32.114028"}
{"question": "Which character is responsible for the 1883 eruption of Krakatoa in \"The Dresden Files\"", "answer": "Ebenezar McCoy", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Dresden_Files_characters", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:09:40.173645"}
{"question": "In what year did Eugene Mahoney change his political affiliation from Republican to Democrat", "answer": "1969", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eugene_T._Mahoney", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:10:26.625111"}
{"question": "During which geological epoch did the extinct fish genus Neopholidophoropsis exist", "answer": "Early Cretaceous", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Neopholidophoropsis", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:11:31.913001"}
{"question": "Who is James Daly's twin brother, both being footballers in England", "answer": "Joel Daly", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/James_Daly_(footballer)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:22:03.721419"}
{"question": "In what year did Arsen Minasian found Gilan's sanatorium", "answer": "1954", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arsen_Minasian", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:24:38.782769"}
{"question": "In what date was the Mount Marshall Road District in Australia first established", "answer": "6 July 1923", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shire_of_Mount_Marshall", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:26:14.560111"}
{"question": "In what year did the African National Congress first call for an academic boycott of South Africa", "answer": "1958", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Academic_boycott_of_South_Africa", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:27:00.043574"}
{"question": "How many described species are there in the genus Acneus", "answer": "4", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Acneus", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:27:46.669116"}
{"question": "In which family does the Dubois's seedeater belong", "answer": "Thraupidae", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dubois%27s_seedeater", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:28:21.795142"}
{"question": "In what year did Sun Jingliang become a member of the Chinese Academy of Engineering", "answer": "1995", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sun_Jingliang", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:28:44.529581"}
{"question": "In what year did Saudi Telecom Company (STC) acquire Oger Telecom", "answer": "2008", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Saudi_Oger", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:29:11.580760"}
{"question": "How many times did FK Slovan Duslo Sala's women's team win the Slovak League", "answer": "4", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/FK_Slovan_Duslo_%C5%A0a%C4%BEa_(women)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:35:03.626265"}
{"question": "In which city and country were the 2017 Asian Indoor and Martial Arts Games held", "answer": "Ashgabat, Turkmenistan", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Samoa_at_the_2017_Asian_Indoor_and_Martial_Arts_Games", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:36:18.121773"}
{"question": "In what year was Edward Lorusso's restoration of The Enchanted Cottage completed", "answer": "2024", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Enchanted_Cottage_(1924_film)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:36:44.681949"}
{"question": "How much money did the UK government spend on focus groups and polling to promote the Eat Out to Help Out scheme", "answer": "\u00a32 million", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eat_Out_to_Help_Out", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:37:09.876741"}
{"question": "What company distributed the 2023 film How to Blow Up a Pipeline", "answer": "Neon", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lyrical_Media", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:37:58.809189"}
{"question": "In which district of Moldova is the village of Ciniseuti located", "answer": "Rezina District", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cini%C8%99eu%C8%9Bi", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:40:16.412392"}
{"question": "In what month and year did Heinrich Kubis first begin serving as a flight attendant", "answer": "March 1912", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Heinrich_Kubis", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T05:58:26.225713"}
{"question": "In what century did Procopius Waldvogel live", "answer": "15th-century", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Waldvogel", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:00:04.325692"}
{"question": "In which year and city was the first World University Cycling Championship held", "answer": "1978 in Antwerp, Belgium", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/World_University_Cycling_Championship", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:00:44.976796"}
{"question": "What is the systematic name for the enzyme 2-deoxy-scyllo-inosamine dehydrogenase (SAM-dependent)", "answer": "2-deoxy-scyllo-inosamine:S-adenosyl-L-methionine 1-oxidoreductase", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2-Deoxy-scyllo-inosamine_dehydrogenase_(SAM-dependent)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:01:35.660945"}
{"question": "In what year did Joseph Warren Yost organize the Association of Ohio Architects", "answer": "1885", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Joseph_W._Yost", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:02:05.913164"}
{"question": "What was the first triple version film of India that Sadhana Bose starred in", "answer": "Rajnartaki", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sadhana_Bose", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:02:40.260842"}
{"question": "What open-source software project was GameFace Labs a co-founder of", "answer": "Open Source Virtual Reality (OSVR)", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/GameFace_Labs", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:04:37.190702"}
{"question": "In which town was Australian rugby player Harrison Edwards raised", "answer": "Pacific Palms", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Harrison_Edwards", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:06:56.983828"}
{"question": "In what year did Nils Hesslen become first professor of theology and dean of Lund", "answer": "1794", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nils_Hessl%C3%A9n", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:07:28.590070"}
{"question": "What was the population of Mill Village in the 2020 census", "answer": "394", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mill_Village,_Pennsylvania", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:07:32.671909"}
{"question": "In what date did Shimoichi Station open", "answer": "28 August 1903", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shimoichi_Station", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:08:28.974207"}
{"question": "Who is the former Chancellor of Queen's University Belfast who was also a former United States Senator", "answer": "George Mitchell", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Queen%27s_University_Belfast_people", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:10:04.892259"}
{"question": "Who directed the eighth episode of the seacond season of Dexter, \"Morning Comes\"", "answer": "Keith Gordon", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Morning_Comes_(Dexter)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:11:46.962037"}
{"question": "What was the population of Prhati, Croatia, according to the 2021 census", "answer": "135", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prhati,_Barban", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:13:13.126672"}
{"question": "How many seats did the Socialist Republican Party win in the 1953 Sudanese legislative election", "answer": "3", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Socialist_Republican_Party_(Sudan)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:13:31.678144"}
{"question": "In what month and year was the East India Company ship Bangalore wrecked", "answer": "April 1802", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bangalore_(1792_ship)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:14:20.438640"}
{"question": "Who did Abu Faris imprison when he captured Tlemcen", "answer": "Ibn Khaldun", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Abu_Faris_Abd_al-Aziz_I", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:15:24.499324"}
{"question": "In what date was the Feast of the Holy Name of Jesus inserted into the General Calendar of the Roman Rite", "answer": "20 December 1721", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Feast_of_the_Holy_Name_of_Jesus", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:15:55.891699"}
{"question": "In what year did Peter Schattschneider first publish a Science Fiction story", "answer": "1978", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peter_Schattschneider", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:17:50.783471"}
{"question": "In what year was the Turkish lira first introduced during the Ottoman reign", "answer": "1844", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lira", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:18:40.236650"}
{"question": "At what level did James Connolly start playing rugby with his local club", "answer": "under-7 level", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/James_Connolly_(rugby_union)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:20:00.553825"}
{"question": "What was the population of Daram Rud, Iran, according to the 2006 census", "answer": "43", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Daram_Rud,_Kurdistan", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:20:22.886011"}
{"question": "On what day did Louis LeBourdais marry Kate-Elizabeth Pughe", "answer": "17 April 1912", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Louis_LeBourdais", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:20:55.130283"}
{"question": "As of 2022, what was the largest town in the Republic of Ireland without a Garda station", "answer": "Ratoath", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ratoath", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:21:17.913566"}
{"question": "In what year was the Cathedral of the Holy Cross in Lusaka, Zambia, constructed", "answer": "1962", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cathedral_of_the_Holy_Cross,_Lusaka", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:22:15.934309"}
{"question": "In what century did Buddhism first arrive in Arunachal Pradesh", "answer": "8th century CE", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Religion_in_Arunachal_Pradesh", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:22:47.658683"}
{"question": "How many Selmon brothers who played in the NFL are notable alumni of Eufaula High School", "answer": "3", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eufaula_High_School_(Eufaula,_Oklahoma)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:24:27.298193"}
{"question": "What was the name of the Malagasy lizard species that was named after Maurice de Rothschild", "answer": "Paracontias rothschildi", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maurice_de_Rothschild", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:25:16.172052"}
{"question": "On what platform was the first season of Pequenas coincidencias originally released", "answer": "Amazon Prime Video", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peque%C3%B1as_coincidencias", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:25:53.269028"}
{"question": "What was the total value of assets seized from La Rosa in the 2011 Guardia di Finanza operation", "answer": "6 million euros", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/La_Rosa_%27ndrina", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:27:12.674929"}
{"question": "Who played the character of Violet Marchant in the 1916 film A Bunch of Violets", "answer": "Chrissie White", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/A_Bunch_of_Violets_(film)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:27:31.713845"}
{"question": "At which stadium was the women's 100 metres event held during the 1967 Summer Universiade", "answer": "National Olympic Stadium in Tokyo", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Athletics_at_the_1967_Summer_Universiade_%E2%80%93_Women%27s_100_metres", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:28:32.628324"}
{"question": "How many teams participated in the 1950-51 OB I bajnoksag season in Hungary", "answer": "Eight teams", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1950%E2%80%9351_OB_I_bajnoksag_season", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:29:05.554952"}
{"question": "What architectural firm designed the Daniel Webster Robinson House", "answer": "Peabody and Stearns of Boston", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Daniel_Webster_Robinson_House", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:29:51.520939"}
{"question": "What was the population of Karakoyunlu, Turkey, in the 2022 census", "answer": "2,728", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Karakoyunlu", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:31:00.241917"}
{"question": "Which baseball team did Arnoldo Castro manage in the latter part of the 1980 season", "answer": "Tabasco Plataneros", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arnoldo_Castro", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:31:43.608268"}
{"question": "What brand name did KYSX use when it changed to classic country format in December 2012", "answer": "Twang 105.1", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/KYSX", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:32:41.802814"}
{"question": "How many Cessna 208 Caravans were operating in military service as of 2024", "answer": "123", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cessna_208_Caravan", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:32:58.283698"}
{"question": "In what date was retired football player Ryo Tadokoro born", "answer": "8 April 1986", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ryo_Tadokoro", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:33:38.525044"}
{"question": "Where is the Syrian Writers Association registered", "answer": "United Kingdom", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Syrian_Writers_Association", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:35:23.040801"}
{"question": "Who played the character of Megan the bartender in the film Remember Me", "answer": "Meghan Markle", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Remember_Me_(2010_film)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:35:52.053022"}
{"question": "In which city did Barrington Francis become a professional boxer", "answer": "Montreal", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Barrington_Francis", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:52:14.574026"}
{"question": "What is the seating capacity of KFF A&N's home ground", "answer": "1,500", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/KFF_A%26N", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:52:48.729479"}
{"question": "Who created and co-directed the Ugandan web series Mela", "answer": "Nana Kagga", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mela_(Ugandan_TV_series)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:53:21.374725"}
{"question": "Who was the Byzantine empress Gregoria's father", "answer": "Niketas", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gregoria", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:53:51.311064"}
{"question": "In which voivodeship is the village of Kunkowa located", "answer": "Lesser Poland Voivodeship", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kunkowa", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:55:41.539405"}
{"question": "At which college did Nicholas Ray present a film and give a lecture, with excerpts featured in Lightning Over Water", "answer": "Vassar College", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lightning_Over_Water", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:56:40.989570"}
{"question": "When was the Belgian cycling manager Christophe Sercu born", "answer": "16 October 1970", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Christophe_Sercu", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:57:07.418975"}
{"question": "In which year was the Nee Soon Central Single Member Constituency of Singapore merged into Nee Soon Group Representation Constituency", "answer": "2011", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nee_Soon_Central_Single_Member_Constituency", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:58:26.367647"}
{"question": "What is the radioactive isotope used to tag iodopindolol", "answer": "iodine-125", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Iodopindolol", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T06:59:39.741395"}
{"question": "In what year was the first iron forge founded in Ulft", "answer": "1754", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ulft", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T07:00:15.296654"}
{"question": "In what year did Chris Hung win the International Composition Competition in Sofia, Bulgaria", "answer": "2013", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chris_Hung_(composer)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T07:01:01.266978"}
{"question": "In what year did Habib University's first class of undergraduate students begin", "answer": "August 2014", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Habib_University", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T07:02:18.523862"}
{"question": "In what year was the Chateau de Saint-Ferriol listed as a \"monument historique\" by the French Ministry of Culture", "answer": "1999", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ch%C3%A2teau_de_Saint-Ferriol", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T07:03:11.611230"}
{"question": "In which taxonomic family does the Orizabus pyriformis belong", "answer": "Scarabaeidae", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orizabus_pyriformis", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T07:04:31.906274"}
{"question": "How many consecutive Swedish javelin throwing titles did Sven Daleflod win", "answer": "4", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sven_Daleflod", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T07:05:14.330384"}
{"question": "In which book did Bianca Allaine discover her love for the macabre at a young age", "answer": "Scary Stories to Tell in the Dark", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bianca_Allaine", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:13:10.940103"}
{"question": "In which country did a massive stranding of 337 dead whales occur in a remote fjord in 2015", "answer": "Chile", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cetacean_stranding", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:13:18.021827"}
{"question": "How many species are recognized in the Calystegia genus", "answer": "25", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Calystegia", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:13:20.759333"}
{"question": "How many languages did James Michael Gardner Fell know", "answer": "7 (Sanskrit, Icelandic, German, French, Russian, Greek, and Latin)", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/James_Michael_Gardner_Fell", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:13:28.552951"}
{"question": "At which college did Rob McCord do a year abroad during his Harvard studies", "answer": "Trinity College in Ireland", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rob_McCord", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:13:37.769082"}
{"question": "What is the specific point of land named after the first European to explore the Hanover area", "answer": "Logan's Point", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hanover,_Indiana", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:27:02.378701"}
{"question": "In what year was the FIBA U18 EuroBasket competition first inaugurated", "answer": "1964", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/FIBA_U18_EuroBasket", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:27:09.089085"}
{"question": "What was the total number of prisoners transported to Auschwitz on the first mass transport on 14 June 1940", "answer": "728", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/First_mass_transport_to_Auschwitz_concentration_camp", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:33:19.896398"}
{"question": "Who is the well-known naturalist and television presenter that attended Bitterne Park School", "answer": "Chris Packham", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bitterne_Park_School", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:33:22.878786"}
{"question": "Who did Charles V recognize as the rightful king of Denmark and Norway in the Treaty of Speyer", "answer": "Christian III", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Treaty_of_Speyer_(1544)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:33:26.025697"}
{"question": "How many miles long is the M-47 highway in Michigan", "answer": "14.328 miles (23.059 km)", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/M-47_(Michigan_highway)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:33:29.302390"}
{"question": "What rugby team does Kaleb Trask play for in Super Rugby", "answer": "Chiefs", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kaleb_Trask", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:33:32.170026"}
{"question": "How many swimming pools does the Country Club at Wakefield Plantation have", "answer": "3", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Country_Club_at_Wakefield_Plantation", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:33:35.139622"}
{"question": "What does the genus name Myocastor literally mean in English", "answer": "mouse-beaver", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nutria", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:33:39.030742"}
{"question": "What film did Paul Stewart serve as music supervisor for that won an Academy Award", "answer": "Hustle & Flow", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Paul_Stewart_(music_producer)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:33:48.279036"}
{"question": "What is the elevation of Shengena Peak in the Same District", "answer": "2,463 m", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Same_District,_Kilimanjaro", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:36:35.057069"}
{"question": "How many performances did the original 1932 Broadway production of Dinner at Eight have", "answer": "232", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dinner_at_Eight_(play)", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:36:38.204324"}
{"question": "In what month and year did the Howard Handball Team participate in the Partille Cup in Sweden", "answer": "July 2013", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Howard_High_School,_Mazowe", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:37:27.255735"}
{"question": "How many months in prison was Iso H sentenced for refusing to enlist in the Finnish defence force", "answer": "six and a half months", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Iso_H", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:37:30.119197"}
{"question": "What was the name of Frank Wigglesworth Clarke's mother", "answer": "Abby (Fisher) Clarke", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Frank_Wigglesworth_Clarke", "timestamp": "2025-08-28T11:38:32.011232"}
{"question": "In what year did Bruce Jeffery marry Margaret", "answer": "6 January 1968", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bruce_Jeffery", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:22:04.260523"}
{"question": "Who directed the 1939 Czech comedy film Dívka v modrém", "answer": "Otakar Vávra", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/D%C3%ADvka_v_modr%C3%A9m", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:22:09.268458"}
{"question": "In what month and year was 80% of Biflex Products Corporation's common stock acquired by General Spring Bumper Corporation", "answer": "March 1929", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Biflex_Products_Corporation", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:22:16.231514"}
{"question": "At which venue were the 2014 South American Games field hockey competitions held", "answer": "Club Deportivo Manquehue in Santiago, Chile", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Field_hockey_at_the_2014_South_American_Games", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:22:19.610955"}
{"question": "In what year was Montague North appointed as Rector of Sternfield, Suffolk", "answer": "1767", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Montague_North", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:22:25.038323"}
{"question": "Who directed the 1993 Kannada comedy drama film Hendthi Helidare Kelabeku", "answer": "Relangi Narasimha Rao", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hendthi_Helidare_Kelabeku", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:22:31.694408"}
{"question": "In what year did The Nebraska Club move to the First National Bank building", "answer": "1970", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Nebraska_Club", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:22:34.561728"}
{"question": "At what temperature did John William Draper establish the Draper point in 1847", "answer": "798 K (525 °C; 977 °F)", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Draper_point", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:22:37.838829"}
{"question": "In which city was the Standard Dictionary of Facts published", "answer": "Buffalo", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Standard_Dictionary_of_Facts", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:22:40.807992"}
{"question": "In what year was Black Butte Dam constructed", "answer": "1963", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stony_Creek_(Sacramento_River_tributary)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:22:46.440210"}
{"question": "In what year was the Fish Creek railway station closed", "answer": "1992", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fish_Creek_railway_station", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:22:50.638642"}
{"question": "What length is the main swimming pool at Easton Leisure Centre", "answer": "25 metres (82 feet)", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Easton_Leisure_Centre", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:22:53.454838"}
{"question": "At what age did David N. Donihue write his first play that was produced in Seattle", "answer": "18", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/David_N._Donihue", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:23:01.595427"}
{"question": "In which university is Aya Imai a third-year student as of February 2023", "answer": "Doshisha University", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aya_Imai", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:23:05.589690"}
{"question": "In what year did James Cleugh publish the book 'Spain in the Modern World'", "answer": "1953", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/James_Cleugh", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:24:07.173424"}
{"question": "In the 2016 census, how many households did Rumeshkan Rural District have", "answer": "2,130", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rumeshkan_Rural_District", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:24:10.102017"}
{"question": "In what year was the body of the 'Gentleman of Heligoland' discovered", "answer": "1994", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Gentleman_of_Heligoland", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:24:13.173846"}
{"question": "In which constituency did Björn Leví Gunnarsson represent the Pirate Party from 2017 to 2024", "answer": "Reykjavík South", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bj%C3%B6rn_Lev%C3%AD_Gunnarsson", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:24:16.348813"}
{"question": "In what year did John Petty FitzMaurice buy Bowood Park", "answer": "1754", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Petty,_1st_Earl_of_Shelburne", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:24:19.522667"}
{"question": "In what year was Elton John's Greatest Hits Volume III initially certified gold by the RIAA", "answer": "February 1989", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elton_John%27s_Greatest_Hits_Vol._3", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:24:23.004358"}
{"question": "On what date was the men's 25 metre rapid fire pistol team competition held during the 2006 Asian Games", "answer": "6 December", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shooting_at_the_2006_Asian_Games_%E2%80%93_Men%27s_25_metre_rapid_fire_pistol_team", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:24:29.762645"}
{"question": "What percentage of electricity generated in Australia was from renewable sources in 2022", "answer": "39.4%", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Energy_in_Australia", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:24:33.449101"}
{"question": "In what year was the Church of the Sacred Heart in Riverstown built", "answer": "1940", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Riverstown", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:24:36.510518"}
{"question": "From which university did Guo Jiakun graduate in 2002", "answer": "Nankai University in Tianjin", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Guo_Jiakun", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:24:42.614420"}
{"question": "In which period did the practice of using toad secretions as treatment begin in traditional Chinese medicine", "answer": "Tang Dynasty (618-907 BC)", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Resibufogenin", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:24:46.249292"}
{"question": "In what year was the Fortingall Yew first recorded in writing", "answer": "1769", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fortingall_Yew", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:24:57.615438"}
{"question": "In which city and region of Japan were the 1990 Asian Winter Games held", "answer": "Sapporo, Hokkaidō", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/India_at_the_1990_Asian_Winter_Games", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:01.007735"}
{"question": "In what year was Jóannes Patursson born", "answer": "1866", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/J%C3%B3annes_(name)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:03.964182"}
{"question": "At which school did Shomie Das teach Prince Charles", "answer": "Gordonstoun School", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shomie_Das", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:07.036830"}
{"question": "Who was the longest-serving mayor of Goodyear, Arizona", "answer": "William O. Arnold, who served from approximately 1989 to 2002", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_mayors_of_Goodyear,_Arizona", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:14.102820"}
{"question": "In which shrine did Nishikifuji Ryūsei get married in Tokyo", "answer": "Tomioka Hachiman Shrine", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nishikifuji_Ry%C5%ABsei", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:17.379095"}
{"question": "In what year was the first recording of 'Shchedryk' made", "answer": "1922", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shchedryk_(song)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:20.528449"}
{"question": "In what year was the German diplomat Friedrich Sthamer born", "answer": "1856", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sthamer", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:23.420712"}
{"question": "In what year was the tunnel at Col de Rousset drilled", "answer": "1979", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Col_de_Rousset", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:26.359414"}
{"question": "In which year did Alfred Ordway become the Director of Exhibitions of the Boston Athenaeum", "answer": "1856", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alfred_Ordway", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:29.564669"}
{"question": "What symbol is used to represent [s] before [e] and [i] in the Êttandâ pal andalûh orthography", "answer": "<ç>", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Standard_for_Andalusian", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:32.739178"}
{"question": "How far is Mottanam from the district headquarters of Erode", "answer": "62 km", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mottanam", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:38.780907"}
{"question": "In what year was the Palm Beach Railway and Power Company incorporated", "answer": "1893", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Palm_Beach_Railway_and_Power_Company", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:41.955535"}
{"question": "In what year did Kiril Denev play his single match for the Bulgaria national football team", "answer": "1926", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kiril_Denev", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:44.822562"}
{"question": "Who provided the narration for R. L. Stine's opening and closing monologues in The Nightmare Room series", "answer": "James Avery of The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air fame", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Nightmare_Room", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:48.099676"}
{"question": "What is the Incident Object Description Exchange Format (IODEF) designed to standardize", "answer": "How incident information is described and exchanged", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Indicator_of_compromise", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:51.207801"}
{"question": "Who defeated Asia Muhammad in the singles final of the 2016 Bendigo Women's International", "answer": "Risa Ozaki", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2016_Bendigo_Women%27s_International", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:54.243953"}
{"question": "What is professional tennis player Monica Niculescu's birth year", "answer": "1987", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Monica_Niculescu", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:25:57.101796"}
{"question": "In which year did Albert Marchinsky first open at the Orpheum Theatre in Denver, Colorado", "answer": "1910", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Albert_Marchinsky", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:00.694627"}
{"question": "In which city was Jorge Carpizo McGregor born", "answer": "San Francisco de Campeche", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jorge_Carpizo_McGregor", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:03.561809"}
{"question": "In what year did Sam Webster win gold medals in all three sprint disciplines at the Junior World Championships", "answer": "2009", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sam_Webster_(cyclist)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:09.808403"}
{"question": "How many families lived in Tag-e Oshtoran during the 2006 census", "answer": "7 families", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tag-e_Oshtoran", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:18.307508"}
{"question": "In what year did Madura Tea first start its production", "answer": "1982", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Madura_Tea_Estates", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:22.832344"}
{"question": "What is the specific title of the first track on the 1969 album Al Verte las Flores Lloran", "answer": "Al verte las flores lloran", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Al_Verte_las_Flores_Lloran", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:26.011358"}
{"question": "In what year was the Broadcast Wave Format (BWF) first specified by the European Broadcasting Union", "answer": "1997", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Broadcast_Wave_Format", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:29.104067"}
{"question": "In which year was Aaron Carter's debut studio album first released in Europe", "answer": "1997", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aaron_Carter_(album)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:32.350599"}
{"question": "In what year did Edward Meyrick describe the moth species Heteralcis holocona", "answer": "1908", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Heteralcis_holocona", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:36.282252"}
{"question": "During which geological period does the Torringen Formation preserve fossils", "answer": "Devonian period", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Torringen_Formation", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:39.299622"}
{"question": "Who were the original writers of the television program Nobody's Watching", "answer": "Bill Lawrence, Neil Goldman, and Garrett Donovan", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nobody%27s_Watching", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:43.293491"}
{"question": "In what month and year did Sir Godfrey Webster marry Elizabeth Vassall", "answer": "1786", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sir_Godfrey_Webster,_4th_Baronet", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:49.336517"}
{"question": "In what year did Sarah Vaughan publish her first novel, The Art of Baking Blind", "answer": "2014", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sarah_Vaughan_(writer)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:52.509348"}
{"question": "In what year was the École Supérieure de Commerce first established", "answer": "1964", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Haute_%C3%89cole_de_Commerce_de_Kinshasa", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:55.786379"}
{"question": "In which year did George Thomas first make his first-class debut for Madras", "answer": "1962", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Thomas_(Indian_cricketer)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:26:58.653448"}
{"question": "In what year was the final episode of Shadows of Fear broadcast", "answer": "1973", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shadows_of_Fear", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:27:11.064183"}
{"question": "In what year did Philip Temple hold the Robert Burns Fellowship at the University of Otago", "answer": "1980", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Philip_Temple", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:27:14.116048"}
{"question": "In what year was the Forest Products Research Laboratory's site at Princes Risborough officially opened", "answer": "31 July 1928", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Forest_Products_Research_Laboratory", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:27:17.392920"}
{"question": "In what season did Erica Rieder serve as the captain of the Manitoba Bisons women's ice hockey team", "answer": "2018-19 season", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Erica_Rieder", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:27:20.362315"}
{"question": "In which specific year did James Phelan kick a 61-yard field goal attempt that bounced off the crossbar", "answer": "1917", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/James_Phelan_(American_football)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:27:30.100882"}
{"question": "In what year was the Eifelwall station first opened", "answer": "1898", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eifelwall/Stadtarchiv_station", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:27:36.336872"}
{"question": "In what year did Mieczysław Palus win his first Polish league championship", "answer": "1949", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mieczys%C5%82aw_Palus", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:27:39.012974"}
{"question": "In what year did Maneklal Sankalchand Thacker become the director general of the Council of Scientific and Industrial Research (CSIR)", "answer": "1955", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maneklal_Sankalchand_Thacker", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:27:42.378688"}
{"question": "In what year did Charles F. Hall first become a member of the Dade County Commission", "answer": "1956", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chuck_Hall_(Florida_politician)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:27:45.553008"}
{"question": "On what date did the 6th Army first encounter Soviet defensive lines during Operation Fischreiher", "answer": "August 17", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Operation_Fischreiher", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:27:53.949730"}
{"question": "In what year did Francesco Berlinghieri begin working on his treatise based on Ptolemy's Geography", "answer": "1464", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Francesco_Berlinghieri", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:27:57.329055"}
{"question": "How many species of Platycorypha are extinct", "answer": "2", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Platycorypha", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:28:04.702096"}
{"question": "In what year was Wilfred Josephs born", "answer": "1927", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Josephs", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:28:07.629438"}
{"question": "In what year did Rajjakuddin Ahmed make his first-class debut for Assam", "answer": "2017", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rajjakuddin_Ahmed", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:28:13.918071"}
{"question": "In what year was the Pakistani sitcom Uff Meri Family released", "answer": "2014", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Uff_Meri_Family", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:28:16.580442"}
{"question": "Who defeated Laura-Ioana Andrei and Mădălina Gojnea in the final of the 2011 Open GDF Suez de Marseille - Doubles tournament", "answer": "Irina-Camelia Begu and Nina Bratchikova", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2011_Open_GDF_Suez_de_Marseille_%E2%80%93_Doubles", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:28:30.497596"}
{"question": "From which constituency in Andhra Pradesh did Sanjeev Kumar represent in the 17th Lok Sabha", "answer": "Kurnool", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sanjeev_Kumar_(Andhra_Pradesh_politician)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:28:33.783813"}
{"question": "In what year was Karl Pruter consecrated as bishop of the Diocese of Boston", "answer": "1967", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Christ_Catholic_Church", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:28:36.568777"}
{"question": "In what year did Alan Pinheiro win the Campeonato Baiano", "answer": "2013", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alan_Pinheiro", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:28:39.313638"}
{"question": "After whom was Aspinwall Lake named", "answer": "Henry Aspinwall", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aspinwall_Lake_(Mahnomen_County,_Minnesota)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:28:42.180904"}
{"question": "In what year was 'The Ugly Duckling' first published", "answer": "1843", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Ugly_Duckling", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:28:48.426932"}
{"question": "What division did PFC Botev Plovdiv return to in the 2012-13 season", "answer": "A Group", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2012%E2%80%9313_PFC_Botev_Plovdiv_season", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:28:54.571150"}
{"question": "In which Oprah Winfrey series did Kelly Neal play the character Abshu Kamau", "answer": "Brewster Place", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kelly_Neal", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:28:57.643128"}
{"question": "In what year did Ibrahim I ibn al-Aghlab name Abu Muhriz as Qadi of Kairouan", "answer": "806", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ibrahim_I_ibn_al-Aghlab", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:29:00.817831"}
{"question": "From which goddess was Khira mohana originally offered at the Jagannath Temple in Puri", "answer": "Lakshmi", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Khiramohana", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:29:03.943982"}
{"question": "On what date was the 1962 Moroccan constitutional referendum held", "answer": "7 December 1962", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1962_Moroccan_constitutional_referendum", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:29:30.319688"}
{"question": "Who was the producer of NCIS: Los Angeles attached to the NCIS: Sydney project in February 2022", "answer": "Shane Brennan", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/NCIS:_Sydney", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:29:33.790962"}
{"question": "In what year did Subodh Chandra Mallik enroll at Trinity College, Cambridge", "answer": "1900", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Subodh_Chandra_Mallik", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:29:36.760377"}
{"question": "In what year was the Khon Buri district officially upgraded to a full district", "answer": "1939", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Khon_Buri_district", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:29:47.512557"}
{"question": "In what year was the Toowong railway station first opened", "answer": "1875", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Toowong_railway_station", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:29:56.016440"}
{"question": "In what year was Henry Spigurnel first sent on a mission to the papal court", "answer": "1311", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Henry_Spigurnel", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:29:59.446966"}
{"question": "In which year did Nans Ducuing make his debut for the France national rugby team", "answer": "2017", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nans_Ducuing", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:30:02.462525"}
{"question": "In what year was F. W. Kickbusch born", "answer": "1841", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kickbusch", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:30:05.397827"}
{"question": "In what year did Septimus J. Hanna become president of the Massachusetts Metaphysical College", "answer": "1910", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Septimus_J._Hanna", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:30:08.607044"}
{"question": "In what year was the historic theater in the Hvar Arsenal constructed", "answer": "1612", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hvar_Arsenal", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:30:11.781513"}
{"question": "In what year was the 4th edition of the Qatari Stars Cup held", "answer": "2012", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2012%E2%80%9313_Qatari_Stars_Cup", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:30:17.925700"}
{"question": "On what date was the EP version of the Pitch Perfect Original Motion Picture Soundtrack released", "answer": "December 18, 2012", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pitch_Perfect_(soundtrack)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:30:20.895163"}
{"question": "Who is the current Chief of the General Staff of the Armed Forces of the Czech Republic", "answer": "Army General Karel Řehka", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chief_of_the_General_Staff_(Czech_Republic)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:30:29.649041"}
{"question": "In what year was the Beccuto Madonna fresco fragment rediscovered", "answer": "1894", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Beccuto_Madonna", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:30:32.568661"}
{"question": "Through which publishing company did Helen Asher publish her novel Tilly's Fortunes", "answer": "Penguin Books", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Helen_Asher", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:30:35.538128"}
{"question": "In what year was the novel Taiko first compiled into volumes by Eiji Yoshikawa's wife", "answer": "1967", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Taiko_(novel)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:30:46.162343"}
{"question": "In which theatre did Pavel Antokolsky work as a director during the 1930s", "answer": "Vakhtangov Theatre in Moscow", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pavel_Antokolsky", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:31:04.732162"}
{"question": "How far is the village of Janów located from the regional capital Białystok", "answer": "39 km (24 mi)", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gmina_Jan%C3%B3w,_Podlaskie_Voivodeship", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:31:07.896859"}
{"question": "In which city did Mike Scott write 'Glastonbury Song'", "answer": "Manhattan", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Glastonbury_Song", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:31:12.431466"}
{"question": "In what year was the York-town Turnpike established", "answer": "1808", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Govans,_Baltimore", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:31:17.318758"}
{"question": "In what year was 425 South Financial Place completed", "answer": "1985", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/425_South_Financial_Place", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:31:20.189799"}
{"question": "From which Indonesian island is the Ambulyx inouei moth species known", "answer": "Sulawesi", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ambulyx_inouei", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:31:23.153948"}
{"question": "From which two cities did Daniel Balaji's parents originate", "answer": "Chittoor and Arcot", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Daniel_Balaji", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:31:26.395479"}
{"question": "On what date was the men's K-1 500 metres sprint canoeing competition held at the 2002 Asian Games", "answer": "12 October", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canoeing_at_the_2002_Asian_Games_%E2%80%93_Men%27s_K-1_500_metres", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:31:29.298766"}
{"question": "According to the 2011 census, what was the population of Radobuđa", "answer": "307", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Radobu%C4%91a", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:31:38.616621"}
{"question": "In which city were the 2022 African Championships in Athletics Men's 200 metres event held", "answer": "Port Louis, Mauritius", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2022_African_Championships_in_Athletics_%E2%80%93_Men%27s_200_metres", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:31:41.688506"}
{"question": "In what year did Mark Zuckerberg and Priscilla Chan announce the creation of the Chan Zuckerberg Initiative", "answer": "1 December 2015", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chan_Zuckerberg_Initiative", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:31:45.375236"}
{"question": "In what year was South Carolina Highway 45 first established as an original state highway", "answer": "1922", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/South_Carolina_Highway_45", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:32:42.115459"}
{"question": "In what century did European art begin depicting Jesus with visible genitalia", "answer": "13th century", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sexuality_and_marital_status_of_Jesus", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:32:45.453193"}
{"question": "In which KBS2 drama did Park Se-wan make her television acting debut in 2016", "answer": "The Red Teacher", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Park_Se-wan", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:32:48.351208"}
{"question": "In which region is the commune of Briant located", "answer": "Bourgogne-Franche-Comté", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Briant,_Sa%C3%B4ne-et-Loire", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:32:51.218820"}
{"question": "In what month and year did Ding Jiemin join the Chinese Communist Party", "answer": "August 1972", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ding_Jiemin", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:32:54.291046"}
{"question": "In what year did Tatiana Yanovskaya become a full professor at Saint Petersburg State University", "answer": "1986", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tatiana_Yanovskaya", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:32:57.158107"}
{"question": "In what year and month was Ronald Reagan Highway officially named after the former president", "answer": "March 17, 1993", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ronald_Reagan_Cross_County_Highway", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:33:04.120981"}
{"question": "In which geographical region is the ground beetle Bembidion nebraskense found", "answer": "North America", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bembidion_nebraskense", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:33:09.036207"}
{"question": "In what year did Virgin Balloon Flights acquire an N-355 balloon manufactured by Ultramagic", "answer": "2006", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Virgin_Balloon_Flights", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:33:12.108723"}
{"question": "In what year did Helen Osborne Storrow buy the brick building on Hull Street that would become the home of Paul Revere Pottery", "answer": "1908", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Paul_Revere_Pottery", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:33:15.796798"}
{"question": "What was the population of Petrovići according to the 2011 census", "answer": "163", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Petrovi%C4%87i,_Nik%C5%A1i%C4%87", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:33:18.436401"}
{"question": "In what year was the Koon House No. 1 listed on the National Register of Historic Places", "answer": "1999", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Koon_House_No._1", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:33:24.294262"}
{"question": "In what year did Raymond Cox become the sole owner of Northfield Construction Company", "answer": "1996", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Raymond_Cox", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:33:30.438025"}
{"question": "How many missions of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints were operating as of June 2024", "answer": "449", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_missions_of_the_Church_of_Jesus_Christ_of_Latter-day_Saints", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:33:33.752163"}
{"question": "In which country is the Leiolepis peguensis (Burmese butterfly lizard) found", "answer": "Myanmar", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leiolepis_peguensis", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:33:38.296738"}
{"question": "From which university did Farkhonda Hassan obtain her PhD in Geology", "answer": "University of Pittsburgh", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Farkhonda_Hassan", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:34:23.379501"}
{"question": "In what year did the Tall Ship pub become a Grade II listed building", "answer": "1998", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Tall_Ship,_Gloucester", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:34:26.451238"}
{"question": "How far west northwest of Morinville is the Edmonton/Morinville (Currie Field) Aerodrome located", "answer": "4 nautical miles (7.4 km; 4.6 mi)", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Edmonton/Morinville_(Currie_Field)_Aerodrome", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:34:29.727942"}
{"question": "Which team won the 2004 Chinese Taipei National Football League championship", "answer": "Taipower", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2004_Chinese_Taipei_National_Football_League", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:34:34.336003"}
{"question": "In what year did Sir Robert Long acquire the manor of Sutton Benger", "answer": "1576", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Long_(soldier)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:34:42.937525"}
{"question": "In what year did Velcheru Narayana Rao earn his Ph.D. from Andhra University", "answer": "1974", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Velcheru_Narayana_Rao", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:35:07.914493"}
{"question": "In what national forest do the headwaters of Cedar Creek originate", "answer": "Mark Twain National Forest", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cedar_Creek_(Bull_Shoals_Lake_tributary)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:35:11.066020"}
{"question": "On which metro line is Cité Amirouche station located", "answer": "Line 1", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cit%C3%A9_Amirouche_Station", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:35:13.965714"}
{"question": "In which college did Christopher Goodman first graduate with a B.A. in 1541", "answer": "Brasenose College, Oxford", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Christopher_Goodman", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:35:17.324809"}
{"question": "In which year was the first documented use of squibs to simulate bullet impacts in cinema", "answer": "1943", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Squib_(explosive)", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:35:25.126397"}
{"question": "From which specific location was Neptunomonas acidivorans isolated", "answer": "Daebu Island sediment", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Neptunomonas_acidivorans", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:35:32.709106"}
{"question": "In what year did residents of Penobscot raise concerns about oyster farming on the Bagaduce River", "answer": "2014", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bagaduce_River", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:35:35.776379"}
{"question": "In what year did Gamaliel Mbonimana publish his book about the history of Rwandan literature", "answer": "2011", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gamaliel_Mbonimana", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:35:38.950920"}
{"question": "In what city was the Yalı Mosque built in 1755", "answer": "İzmir", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1755_in_architecture", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:35:44.992382"}
{"question": "In what year did Val J. Forgett, Jr. found the Navy Arms Company, Inc.", "answer": "1956", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Val_Forgett", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:35:47.859510"}
{"question": "In what year did Chew Chong establish his first shop in New Plymouth", "answer": "1873", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chew_Chong", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:35:50.754917"}
{"question": "In what year was the 1st Buckingham Palace Girl Guide Company first formed", "answer": "1937", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Violet_Synge", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:36:04.960905"}
{"question": "In what year did Șerban Cantacuzino order the famous Romanian edition of the Bible", "answer": "1688", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/%C8%98erban_Cantacuzino", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:36:08.237282"}
{"question": "In what year was the film 'City of Pain' (La città dolente) released", "answer": "1949", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/City_of_Pain", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:36:23.494906"}
{"question": "In what year did Emperor Domitian divide the province of Moesia into Moesia Superior and Moesia Inferior", "answer": "86 AD", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Moesia", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:36:27.240486"}
{"question": "In what year did Bönz Malone write the Notorious B.I.G. cover story for The Source magazine", "answer": "1995", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/B%C3%B6nz_Malone", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:36:33.384078"}
{"question": "Who directed the 1920 silent Western film Shod with Fire", "answer": "Emmett J. Flynn", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shod_with_Fire", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:36:36.909437"}
{"question": "In what season of its history was Aswan SC during the 2020-21 season", "answer": "91st season", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2020%E2%80%9321_Aswan_SC_season", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:36:41.312458"}
{"question": "In what year was Motosaburo Masuyama born", "answer": "1912", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Masuyama", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:36:54.112347"}
{"question": "How many World Series of Poker (WSOP) bracelets has Eli Balas won", "answer": "3", "source": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eli_Balas", "timestamp": "2025-08-29T12:36:57.901501"}
